# **Anthony Super**

720-212-7250 <a href="http://anthony.noided.media">http://anthony.noided.media</a> anthony@noided.media 265 Piñon Hall, Fort Collins, CO 80521 | 3620 W Rosewalk Cir, Highlands Ranch, CO 80129

#### Bio

A developer with 2.5 years experience, primarily working in backend web development using technologies such as Ruby on Rails and Sinatra. I have extensive experience working with databases and automated testing, as well as with using jQuery and React.js on the front end. I am proficient using the command-line on UNIX-like operating systems, and have some experience programming in Java, C++, C, and Objective-C. I also have experience in video editing, primarily using Final Cut Pro.

## **Work Experience**

CEO/LEAD BACKEND DEVELOPER, NOIDED MEDIA LLC - 2014-PRESENT

Founded Noided Media LLC, a web development company. I am its chief backend developer on all of its websites. Its projects include:

- Imagehex, an art sharing website. Ruby on Rails for the backend with Postgres as a
  database. I also wrote quite a bit of React.js for a more satisfying experience on the
  front end.
- Fiction Dock, a fan fiction website. Ruby on Rails for the backend with Postgres as a database.
- WavHead, a democratic DJ that lets anybody at a party vote on what to play next. Ruby with Sinatra, using SQLite as a DB.

#### **INDEPENDENT TECHNICAL SUPPORT – 2012-PRESENT**

Provide technical support and educational services for OS X and Windows. Services included hardware replacement, virus removal, and backup creation.

OPEN SPACE TECHNICIAN, HRMD, HIGHLANDS RANCH, COLORADO – 2015

Worked as a technician improving and repairing the trails around Highlands Ranch.

**BELLA WOMAN'S CARE, VIDEO EDITING, 2014** 

Volunteered and edited promotional material for a Denver-based woman's charity.

### **Achievements**

FBLA NETWORKING CONCEPTS, STATEWIDE SECOND PLACE, 2014

Received second place in the statewide networking concepts test competition from FBLA.

#### **CODE CLUB FOUNDER, THUNDERRIDGE HIGH SCHOOL, 2013-2015**

Founded the programming club at ThunderRidge High School. Acted as its leader and teacher for the duration of the club's existence.

### Education

ThunderRidge High School, HS Diploma – 2015

Colorado State University, Bachelors in Computer Science, Freshman Year – Present

References Available Upon Request